Guide to the Historical Planning publications collection, 1888-2002.
Historical Planning publications collection
- Series II. Highways - Finance, Law, Surveys, Traffic
  - Highways- Traffic- General (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - The Motorist Speaks Summary, July 1, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      American Automobile Association
    - Building Traffic Safety Into Residential Developments (Box 3, Folder 28)
      National Committee for Traffic Safety
  - Highways- Traffic- General (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Highway Traffic Conference Proceedings, April 14, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      Eno Foundation for Highway Traffic Control, Inc.
    - Traffic Survey Manual, January 1, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      Division of Traffic and Safety, Ohio Dept. of Highways
  - Highways- Traffic- General (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Common Sense - The Fundamental of Traffic Safety, February 29, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Automobile Manufacturers Association
    - Uniformity in Highway Traffic Control, January 1, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - The Organization of Official Traffic Agencies in Cities and States, November 1, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - The Speed Problem, November 1, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Every Policeman A Traffic Officer, July 1, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Joseph Kluchesky, 1 page separate insert
  - Highways- Traffic- General (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Fundamentals of Highway Traffic Regulation, January 1, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Traffic Safety Education. A Guidebook for State and Civic Officials, September 1, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - The Evolution of a Uniform Road Traffic Control Code With Safety Rules for Pedestrians, January 1, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Manual on Uniform Traffic Control Devices for Streets and Highways. War Emergency Edition., November 1, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - A Policy on Rotary Intersections, February 1, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Federal Works Agency, Public Roads Administration
    - Wartime Highway Traffic Program (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Highway Traffic Advisory Committee to the War Department
    - Safety for Your Community (Box 4, Folder 2)
      State of Ohio Department of Highways
    - Planned Pedestrian Program, March 1, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      AAA Foundation for Traffic Safety
  - Highways-Traffic-California (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Highway Problems, January 1, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Senate of the State of California
    - The Los Angeles Traffic and Transit Problem, February 1, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Traffic and Parking In the University Avenue Business District (City of Palo Alto, CA), April 1, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Business Districts (Los Angeles County, CA), January 1, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Regional Planning Commission, County of Los Angeles
  - Highways-Traffic-Connecticut (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - U.S. 1 Norwalk Recommended Improvement, May 1, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Connecticut State Highway Department
    - Traffic and Parking Study, Central Business Section, Greenwich, CT, January 1, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Town Plan Commission
    - Traffic Improvement Plan, Waterbury, CT, January 1, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Wilbur Smith and Associates
  - Highways-Traffic-Connecticut (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Traffic Survey. Report and Recommendations. (Westport, CT), January 1, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      National Conservation Bureau, Traffic and Transportation Division
    - Traffic Improvement Plan for Norwalk, CT. v.1, May 21, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Highways-Traffic-Colorado (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Circulation and Land Use Plans (Golden, CO) (Box 4, Folder 6)
      1 map, post 1954.
  - Highways-Traffic-District of Columbia (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Report on the Motor Vehicle and Street Traffic Problem of the District of Columbia, January 1, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      National Capital Park and Planning Commission
    - Traffic Survey. Traffic Conditions in the District of Columbia. Hearings Before the Subcommittee on Streets and Traffic of the Committee on the District of Columbia House Of Representatives., January 1, 1936 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Highways-Traffic-District of Columbia (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - A Preliminary Report on Highway, Parking, and Related Traffic Problems (with Recommendations), January 1, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Department of Highways, District of Columbia
    - District of Columbia Official Traffic Safety Program for 1960, January 1, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - The Metropolitan Area Traffic Council In 1960, January 1, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Appendixes to the Original Wisconsin Avenue Study, January 1, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      U.S. Department of Commerce
    - Increasing the Traffic-Carrying Capacity of Urban Arterial Streets, January 1, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      U.S. Department of Commerce, Bureau of Public Roads
  - Highways-Traffic-Florida (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Extracts From Report on Florida Traffic Survey. Characteristics of Tourist Traffic and Transportation of Citrus Fruit Discusses, June 1, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      Public Roads, v. 16, no. 4
  - Highways-Traffic-Hawaii (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Kamehameha Highway-California Avenue Intersection Traffic Survey, November 1, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Hawaii Territorial Highway Department
  - Highways-Traffic-Idaho (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Origin-Destination Traffic Study (St. Anthony, ID), January 1, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      Idaho Highway Planning Survey, State of Idaho Department of Highways
  - Highways-Traffic-Illinois (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Thirty-fifth Annual Report of Division of Highways, January 1, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Expressway Influence on Parallel Routes (Cook County, IL), July 1, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      Cook County Highway Department
  - Highways-Traffic-Louisiana (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - A Traffic Survey. New Orleans Metropolitan Area. 1944-45, January 1, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      Louisiana Department of Highways.
    - Lake Charles Traffic Survey, January 1, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Highways-Traffic-Maine (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - A Summary of the Lewiston-Auburn Traffic and Parking Survey (Box 4, Folder 14)
      Maine State Highway Commission, post 1958
    - Lewiston-Auburn Traffic and Parking Survey, January 1, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      Maine State Highway Commission
  - Highways-Traffic-Maryland (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Report of the Traffic Study. Annapolis., January 1, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      State of Maryland State Roads Commission
    - Report of the Traffic Survey. Hagerstown (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Traffic and You., January 1, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      Planning Commission of Baltimore
  - Highways-Traffic-Massachusetts (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Consolidated Traffic Report (Including Public Opinion Poll on the Traffic Problem)., January 1, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      Future Springfield Inc.
    - Traffic Study. (Springfield, MA), September 1, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Traffic Report. City of Waltham., January 1, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Average Daily Traffic Flow In 1939., January 1, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      City of Cambridge, City Planning Board, 1 map.
  - Highways-Traffic-Michigan (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Vehicular Traffic in the Business District of Detroit, October 15, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      Rapid Transit Commission.
    - City of Detroit Vehicular Traffic in 1925., October 8, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Detroit Metropolitan Area Traffic Study. Data Summary and Interpretation. Part 1., July 1, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      Separate maps inserted.
    - Detroit Metropolitan Area Traffic Study. Future Traffic and A Long Range Expressway Plan. Part 1., March 1, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Highways-Traffic-Minnesota (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - The Economic Effects of a Highway Change on Faribault, Minnesota, October 1, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      University of Minnesota, Departments of Agricultural Economics and Geography
    - A Highway Change In Changing Faribault, September 1, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Dale Gustafson, Everett G. Smith Jr., Minnesota Highway Research Project, University of Minnesota
    - How Farmers Adjusted to An Interstate Highway in Minnesota, September 1, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Traffic Signs and Obstructions (St. Paul, MN), January 1, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Central Minneapolis Cordon Count - 1958, January 1, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      City of Minneapolis Planning Commission
  - Highways-Traffic-Mississippi (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Brookhaven 1959 Traffic Survey and Street Inventory, April 15, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Highways-Traffic-Missouri (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Application of Origin and Destination Traffic Data in Planning Highway Facilities for Greater Kansas City, January 25, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      John M. Picton, Chief Planning Engineer, Kansas City, MO
    - Rolla, Missouri Traffic Survey, January 1, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Missouri State Highway Department
    - Summary of Metropolitan Origin and Destination Survey (Kansas City, MO), March 30, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Downtown Committee of the Chamber of Commerce
  - Highways-Traffic-New Hampshire (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Portsmouth, New Hampshire, Traffic Survey, 1946, January 1, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      New Hampshire State Highway Department
  - Highways-Traffic-New Jersey (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - A Time Study of Traffic Flow on the New Jersey High-Level Viaduct (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Lawrence S. Tuttle, Public Roads. A Journal of Highway Research., U.S. Department of Agriculture, v. 14, no.12
    - Parking in the Newark Central Business District, January 1, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Bureau of Municipal Research
    - A Plan of Highways for Passaic County, December 1, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Passaic County Planning Board
    - Also in Oversized folder (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Highways-Traffic-New Mexico (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Las Cruces Traffic Study, January 1, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      New Mexico State Highway Department
    - Highway Needs & Highway Dollars, 1965-1971, January 1, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Highways - Traffic - New York - New York City (Oversized), 1945 (Box 70)
  - Highways - Traffic - New York - New York City (Oversized), 1945 (Box 70)
  - Highways - Traffic - New York - New York City (Oversized), 1947 (Box 70)
  - Highways-Traffic-Ohio--New York (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Frigidaire Traffic Survey, Montgomery County, Ohio, Report 4, October 1, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Montgomery County Planning Commission, Ohio
    - Trend of Traffic on Needmore Road Bridge, June 12, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - The Needs of Westchester County Parkways From a Through Traffic Standpoint, November 8, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Westchester County Park Plan Commission, New York, (2 maps loosely inserted)
    - Report of the Traffic Committee on Traffic Survey, April 3, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Rochester Engineering Society, New York.
  - Highways-Traffic- Pennsylvania (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Progress. Published to Promote the Pittsburgh Plan., February 1, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Citizens Committee
    - Traffic and Parking Survey (Marcus Hook Borough), November 1, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Delaware County Planning Commission
    - By-Pass Highways for Traffic Relief, December 1, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      The Highway Committee of the Regional Planning Federation of the Philadelphia Tri-State District
    - Philadelphia 1958 Traffic Accident Facts, January 1, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Department of Streets, Philadelphia.
  - Highways-Traffic- Rhode Island (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - A Traffic Survey of the Providence Metropolitan Area, January 1, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      State of Rhode Island Department of Public Works
    - Highways-Traffic- Texas (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Effects of the Dallas Central Expressway on Land Values and Land Use, September 1, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      William G. Adkins, Texas Transportation Institute
    - El Paso Metropolitan Area Traffic Survey 1958, January 1, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Texas Highway Department, Planning Survey Division
  - Highways-Traffic- Virginia (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Traffic Survey. City of Hampton., June 1, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      Loose Hand Colored Map Inside.
    - Tri-City Traffic Survey (Norfolk, Portsmouth, South Norfolk), January 1, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      5 maps folded inside
  - Highways-Traffic-Washington-West Virginia (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - County Traffic Studies (Washington State), January 1, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      Joint Fact-Finding Committee on Highways, Streets, and Bridges, Division of Industrial Research, State College of Washington
    - Traffic Survey Report and Recommendations, Parkersburg, West Virginia, January 1, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      Traffic Engineering Division, National Conservation Bureau
    - Traffic Survey Report of Welch, West Virginia, January 1, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      State Road Commission of West Virginia, Planning Division
  - Highways-Traffic-Wisconsin (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - A Plan for University Avenue (Madison, Wisconsin), September 1, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      Barton Aschman Associates Inc.
    - Origin-Destination Traffic Survey, Milwaukee Metropolitan Area, January 1, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      State Highway Commission of Wisconsin, U.S. Public Roads Administration
    - Traffic Census Report (Milwaukee, WI), November 23, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      Board of Public Land Commissioners
    - Traffic Survey, Racine., January 1, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      State Highway Commission of Wisconsin; Bureau of Public Roads, U.S. Department of Commerce
    - Tables Accompanying the Report of the Madison Traffic Survey, January 1, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Highways - Traffice - Wisconsin (Oversized), 1951 (Box 69)
  - Highways-Traffic-Foreign- Canada (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Traffic Survey, City of Montreal., February 1, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 13)
      City Planning Department
    - Traffic Survey, City of Montreal, A Programme, February 27, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Traffic Survey, City of Montreal, Analysis of the Results of Four Years' Counts - 1945, 1946, 1947, 1948., July 1, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Highways-Traffic-Foreign- Great Britain (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Basic Road Statistics, Great Britain and Northern Ireland, 1956, September 1, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Basic Road Statistics, Great Britain and Northern Ireland, 1957, September 1, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Basic Road Statistics, Great Britain and Northern Ireland, 1958, September 1, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - London Traffic 1957, July 1, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      Ministry of Transport and Civil Aviation
    - A Plan to Combat Congestion in Central London, July 1, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      London County Council
  - Highways - Expressways - New York City, 1930 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Highways - Expressways - New York City, 1920-1950 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Highways - Expressways - New York City, 1930-1950 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Highways - Expressways - New York City, 1930-1950 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Highways - Highways, 1940-1960 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Highways - Expressways - New York City, 1930,150-1960 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Highways - Expressways - Ohio, 1944 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Highways - Expressways - Pennsylvania, 1930-40,60 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Highways - Expressways - West Virginia, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Highways - Expressways - Milwaukee (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Highways - Expressways - Puerto Rico, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Highways - Expressways - Canada, 1940 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Highways - Expressways - Foreign - Germany (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Highways - Expressways - Foreign - Great Britain (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Highways - Finance - General, 1930,1950 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Highways - Finance - General, 1950-1960 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Highways - Finance - Arizona, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Series III. History
  - History- U.S. - General (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Twenty Years of City Planning Progress in the United States, January 1, 1927 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      John Nolen, National Conference on City Planning
    - Olmsted and Kimball. A List of City Planning Reports, December 1, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - History- U.S. - California - District of Columbia (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Map of Modesto, Stanislaus County, California, 1888 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Planning for "Core Area" Development in Sacramento, California's Capitol City, March 15, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Sacramento City Planning Commission
    - The Changing Scene. A 100-Year Picture History of Southern California., January 1, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      W.W. Robinson, Pioneer Savings and Loan Association
    - Sesquicentennial of the United States Capitol, October 1, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      H. Paul Caemmerer, Reprinted from the South Atlantic Quarterly, v. 42, no. 4
  - History- U.S. - Illinois (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Historical Information About Chicago., September 26, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Frederick Rex
  - History- U.S. - New Jersey - New York (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Teaneck New Jersey. Forty Years of Progress. 1895- 1935., January 1, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - A History of City Planning In Rochester., October 1, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Blake McKelvey, Rochester History, vol. 6, no. 4
    - New York. 1653-1953, February 1, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      New York Times Magazine.
  - History- U.S. - South Carolina - Tennessee (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Our Charleston. 1700 - 1860 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Junior League of Charleston, Inc.
    - 100th Anniversary. Nashville Chamber of Commerce. 1947., January 1, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Nashville Chamber of Commerce.
    - Nashville. Its Personality and Progress. 1779-1956, May 2, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - History- U.S. - Texas and Wisconsin (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - A Short History of Northeast El Paso (Texas), October 1, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      City of El Paso, Texas, Department of Planning
    - A Short History of Northwest El Paso (Texas), December 1, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - A Short History of South El Paso (Texas), October 1, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - A Short History of Ysleta (Texas), February 1, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - History of Planning Activity in Milwaukee, 1892-1952, March 1, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      Board of Public Land Commissioners (Wisconsin)
  - History- Foreign- Canada (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Early Days in the Ottawa Country, January 1, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      National Capital Commission
- Series IV. Hospitals and Hospital Districts
  - Hospitals and Hospital Districts - General (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - The Spatial Structure of the Medical Care Process., July 1, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Jerry B. Schneider, Regional Science Research Institute
    - A New Approach to the Delineation of Hospital Service Areas, August 1, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      H.D. Cherniak and Jerry B. Schneider, Regional Science Research Institute
    - Hospital Administrative Research, June 1, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare
    - Hospital Central Services. A Survey of Current Literature. Volume 1., January 1, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Hospital Outpatient Services. Volume I. Selected References Annotated., July 1, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Hospital Emergency Service. Criteria for Organization., January 1, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - The Progressive Patient Care Hospital. Estimating Bed Needs., January 1, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Hospital Equipment Checklist (Group I - Built-In), January 1, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Hill Burton Publications. An Annotated Bibliography., January 1, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - The Case for Decentralizing Cook County Hospital - Some Applications of Linear Optimization in Hospital Planning. Chicago Regional Hospital Study., January 1, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Robert Earickson, University of Washington.
    - Relationship Between Transportation and Hospital Location and Utilization., July 1, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Richard Morrill
    - Hospital, Physician and Commercial Location, December 1, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Richard Morrill and Robert Earickson
    - Opportunities for Planning and Constructing Medical, Mental Retardation, and Other Health Facilities, November 13, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Facts about the Hill-Burton Program. The Hospital and Medical Facilities Construction Program Under Title VI of the Public Health Service Act, June 30, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Hospitals and Hospital Districts - U.S. - Colorado- District of Columbia (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Concerning Creation of Hospital Districts. Senate Bill No. 256, May 11, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      State of Colorado.
    - Report of the Consultant Committee on the Development of a Master Plot Plan for the National Institutes of Health, June 1, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Hospitals and Hospital Districts - U.S. - Illinois (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Report of the Medical Center Commission to the 71st General Assembly of Illinois, January 1, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      Medical Center Commission. Illinois.
    - Michael Reese Hospital Planning Report. 1956., November 12, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Hospitals and Hospital Districts - U.S. - Kentucky - Michigan (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Preliminary Louisville Area Hospital Survey Made For Louisville Area Development Association, November 1, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      F.R. Bradley, M.D. and R.E. Raper
    - The Detroit Medical Center, June 1, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      Michigan Society of Architects
    - Detroit Medical Center Issue, July 1, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      The Harper Star, vol 14, no. 7
  - Hospitals and Hospital Districts - U.S. - North Carolina- Wisconsin (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - A Metropolitan Community Survey to Evaluate Hospitals and Medical Care Facilities, Public and Private Welfare Agencies, and Public Health Facilities and Services, and to Recommend Programs to Meet These Community Needs for the Decade, 1960 - 1970. Section 1. Hospitals and Medical Care Facilities of Mecklenburg County, North Carolina., October 1, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      John W. Rankin
    - The Changing Distribution and Adequacy of Medical, Dental, and Hospital Services in Rural and Urban Communities in Wisconsin, 1910-1960., May 1, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      Gordon L. Bultena, Dept. of Rural Sociology, University of Wisconsin
  - Hospitals and Hospital Districts - Foreign- South Africa (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Clinics and Hospitals as Community Facilities in Residential Areas, January 1, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      A. Jennings, W.Z. Swart
  - Hospitals - Research, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Series V. Housing
  - Housing- General - 1920s-1930s (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - The Housing Situation and the Way Out, December 1, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Lawrence Veiller, National Housing Association, Reprinted from Architectural Record
    - Federal Emergency Administration of Public Works, Housing Division. Status of Projects- June 1, 1937., June 1, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      H.A. Gray, Director of Housing
    - To Meet the Housing Needs of the Lower Income Groups. A Tentative Program for Federal Cooperation with Local Governments and Private Enterprise, January 1, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Frederic A. Delano, The American City
    - The American Program of Low-Rent Public Housing, January 1, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      Federal Emergency Administration of Public Works
    - Housing Study Bulletin. Issues 2, 4-9, July 1, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      The Housing Study Guild (issues bound together)
    - Planning for Low Rent Housing, January 1, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      National Association of Housing Officials
    - The Fibre of the Nation (Box 7, Folder 15)